♪♪♪
♪ We all came out to Montreux ♪
♪ On the Lake Geneva shoreline ♪
♪ To make records
with a mobile ♪
♪ We didn't have much time ♪
♪ Frank Zappa and the Mothers ♪
♪ Were at the best
place around ♪
♪ But some stupid
with a flare gun ♪
♪ Burned the place
to the ground ♪
♪ Smoke on the water,
a fire in the sky ♪
♪ Smoke on the water ♪
♪ They burned down the
gambling house ♪
♪ It died with an awful sound ♪
♪ Funky Claude was running
in and out ♪
♪ Pulling kids out the ground ♪
♪ When it all was over ♪
♪ We had to find another place ♪
♪ The Swiss time was running
out ♪
♪ It seemed that we would
lose the race ♪
♪ Smoke on the water,
a fire in the sky ♪
♪ Smoke on the water ♪
♪ We ended up at
the Grand Hotel ♪
♪ It was empty, cold and bare ♪
♪ But with the Rolling truck
Stones thing just outside ♪
♪ Making our music there ♪
♪ With a few red lights,
a few old beds ♪
♪ We made a place to sweat ♪
♪ No matter what we
get out of this ♪
♪ I know, I know we'll
never forget ♪
♪ Smoke on the water,
a fire in the sky ♪
♪ Smoke on the water ♪
♪ Woo, yeahhhhhh ♪
♪ Burn, burn, burn, burn,
burn up in the sky ♪
♪ Ahhhhhhhhhhh ♪
♪♪♪
Ah, break a leg Frank.